spikehumer.com 2013-03-12

# Privacy Policy | Spike Humer

Spike Humer International is committed to protecting your privacy. Any personal information collected by Spike Humer International will not be transferred to or shared with any third party without your consent. Spike Humer International uses safe, secure 3rd party provider technology to protect your personal information.

Personal information may be used by Spike Humer International to communicate with our customers and subscribers, fulfill orders, improve customer service and also for editorial purposes. Spike Humer International may also use personal information to send updates about new products and promotions, provided the user has explicitly requested such updates. Users may unsubscribe from these updates at any time by clicking on the ‘UnSubscribe’ link at the bottom of any email from Spike Humer International.

Email addresses submitted to Spike Humer International will remain the private property of Spike Humer International and will not be sold to any third party.

Spike Humer International reserves the right to amend this privacy policy at any time. Amendments to this policy will be posted on our web site in a timely manner.

The Spike Humer International is committed to delivering you high quality training on time according to the agreed schedule. All product delivery will be electronic and you will have the opportunity to download the content to your own PC to consume as is convenient.

Any personal information collected by Spike Humer International will not be transferred to or shared with any third party without your consent. Spike Humer International uses safe, secure 3rd party provider technology to protect your personal information.

Credit Card transactions are performed securely using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technologies. Credit card transactions for international customers purchasing in US Dollars will be processed by PowerPay and no credit card details will be stored on Spike Humer International sites.
